Guide to the the Richard W. Lyman, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0215
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Accession 1982-052
  - Committee of Fifteen, 3/78 - 12/79; C9.2 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Honor Code Commission, 1/79 - 7/80; C9.5 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Administrative Panel on Privacy of Information, 3/79 - 11/79; C11 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Presidential Search: Public Information, 1/69 - 5/80; C12 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Search Committees, misc., 8/79 - 6/80; C12 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees, misc., 1/80 - 7/80; Bl (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Board of Trustees, misc., 9/73 - 12/79; Bl (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Stanford Cabinet, 1/79 - 3/80; B9 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - President, Board of Trustees, 5/79 - 4/80; B11 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings/Schedules, 3/79 - 7/80; B13 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Board of Trustees Agendas and Pre-Board Agendas, 6/79 - 11/79; B13.3 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees, 1/72 - 6/80; B13.4 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Deceased Former Trustee Files: Charles R. Blythe, James F. Crafts, Benjamin S. Crocker, Paul Edwards, Fred H. Merril, George Morell, Homer Spence, Flora Lamson Hewlett (Box 13, Folder 310)
  - Stanford Misc., Stanfordania, 9/77 - 6/80; PAD 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports (Admin. and Academic), 8/72 - 8/79; PAD 1.6.3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Organization, 1/74 - 1/80; PAD 1.6.4 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Signature Resolutions/Authorizations, 3/80 - 8/80; PAD 1.6.5 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - University Policy, Misc. Matters, 3/75 - 6/80; PAD 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Facilities for the Handicapped, 5/77 - 7/80; PAD 2.11 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Alcoholism, 9/76 - 5/80; PAD 2.15/1 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Misuse of Stanford Name, 8/78 - 1/79; PAD 2.17 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Higher Education, Misc., 5/79 - 8/80; PAD 2.27 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Guide, 4/76 - 8/80; PAD 3.2 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - University Calendar/Holidays, 8/79 - 2/80; PAD 3.21 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Presidential Staff Meetings, 9/78 - 6/80; PAD 4.11 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Vice-Presidential Group, 1/78 - 5/80; PAD 4.12 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Public Affairs Office, 2/79 - 3/80; PAD 4.22 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Ombudsman, 11/78 - 6/80; PAD 6 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Admissions Office, 8/80 - 10/79; PAD 8.1 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Bakke Case (Admissions Policy), 6/77 - 2/80; PAD 8.1.1/1 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - College Work-Study Program, 10/79 - 6/80; PAD 8.7.2 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Dean of Student Affairs, 10/78 - 8/80; PAD 8.8 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Student Services and Special Services, 1/79 - 1/80; PAD 8.8.2 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Exchange Programs, 8/78 - 12/79; PAD 8.10 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Stanford Overseas Studies, 1/79 - 8/80; PAD 8.11 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Stanford Program in Berlin, 4/79 - 7/79; PAD 8.11.4/1 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Stanford Program in Bonn, 7/79; PAD 8.11.4/2 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Financial Aids, 3/79 - 5/80; PAD 8.12 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Student Loans, 11/79 - 5/80; PAD 8.12.1 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Graduate Student Financial Aid, 5/79 - 5/80; PAD 8.12.2 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 6/78 - 8/80; PAD 8.18 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Hanna-Honeycomb House, 10/75 - 10/77; PAD 8.18.2 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Buck Estate, 8/79 - 2/80; PAD 8.18.4 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Fraternities/Sororities, 4/80 - 6/80; PAD 8.18.8 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Housing for Students, 8/79 - 7/80; PAD 8.18.11 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Registrar, 9/78 - 8/80; PAD 8.21 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Minority Enrollment, 8/73 - 5/80; PAD 8.21.2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Minorities, 7/79 - 3/80; PAD 9 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Black Affairs, 2/79 - 11/79; PAD 9.1 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Black Affairs, 8/78 - 8/80; PAD 9.1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Chicano Affairs, 4/80 - 5/80; PAD 9.2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Asst. to the Pres. for Chicano Affairs, 12/79 - 7/80; PAD 9.2.1 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 8/75 - 8/80; PAD 9.6 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action (OFCCP), 9/79 - 3/80; PAD 9.6 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Task Force on Women, 1/80 - 6/80; PAD 9.6.1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Personnel & Employee Relations, 3/79 - 8/80; PAD 10 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Staff Development Programs, 3/74 - 11/79; PAD 10.2 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Policy: Appointment of Lecturers and other Short-term Teachers, 2/79 - 5/80; PAD 10.6 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Committee for Art, 10/73 - 2/80; PAD 10.7.4 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Child Care, 10/72 - 8/80; PAD 10.7.5 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - United Stanford Employees, 9/79 - 8/80; PAD 10.7.8 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Personnel Policies, 3/79 - 8/80; PAD 10.8 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Faculty/Staff Fringe Benefits, 9/79 - 8/80; PAD 10.8.9 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Grievance Procedures: Faculty/Staff, 8/79 - 12/79; PAD 10.8.10 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Grievance Procedures: Faculty/Staff, 1/76 - 8/79; PAD 10.8.10 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Grievance Hearings: Cases, 1/80 - 7/80; PAD 10.8.10/1 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Grievance: Walker/James, 5/80 - 7/80; PAD 10.8.10/1 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Grievance: Tetteh Kofi, 11/77 - 8/80; PAD 10.8.10/1 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Grievance Hearings: Cases, 2/79 - 12/79; PAD 10.8.10/1 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Grievance: Gilda Loew, 5/79 - 10/79; PAD 10.8.10/1 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Grievance: Robert Bernard, 3/78 - 1/79; PAD 10.8.10/2 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Grievances: Student/Faculty on Acad. Matter, 10/78 - 3/79; PAD 10.8.10/3 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Retirement, 10/78 - 7/80; PAD 10.8.17 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Early Retirement, 9/78 - 7/80; PAD 10.8.17/1 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - TIAA/CREF and Prudential, 3/76 - 9/79; PAD 10.8.17/3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Salaries, 9/79 - 3/80; PAD 10.8.19 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Salaries, 1/79 - 5/80; PAD 10.8.19 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Tuition Benefit Plan, 4/79 - 6/80; PAD 10.8.22 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Service Operations, 9/78 - 7/80; PAD 11.4 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Energy: Information, Misc., 8/77- 8/80; PAD 11.4.2 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Policy Services, 10/78 - 8/80; PAD 11.6 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Commencement, 6/78 - 8/80; PAD 11.7.2 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Publications, Misc., 9/78 - 12/78; PAD 11.8.11 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Television Instructional Network, 10/78 - 8/80; PAD 11.8.13 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Business and Finance, 2/79 - 8/80; PAD 12.2 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Auditing, 1/77 - 1/79; PAD 12.4 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Budgets, 1/79 - 8/80; PAD 12.5 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Tuition, 12/78 - 6/80; PAD 12.5.4 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Wage and Price Freeze Issue, 1/79 - 6/80; PAD 12.5.5 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Insurance/Risk Management, 2/72 - 7/80; PAD 12.8 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Health and Safety, 11/78 - 6/80; PAD 12.8.1 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Office of Development, 11/79 - 3/80; PAD 12.10.1 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Office of Development, 1/79 - 12/79; PAD 12.10.1 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Gift Policies: Gift Summaries, 9/78 - 8/80; PAD 12.10.3/5 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Hewlett, William R., 10/78 - 4/80; PAD 12.10.3/5-29 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - I.B.M., 10/78 - 5/79; PAD 12.10.3/5-51 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Prospective Donors, 1/75 - 7/80; PAD 12.10.3/12 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - University Seminars, 9/78 - 11/79; PAD 12.10.3/13 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Exxon Education Foundation (Esso), 12/78 - 11/79; PAD 12.10.4/67 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Fleishman Foundation, 11/78 - 10/79; PAD 12.10.4/69 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Fluor Foundation, 11/74 - 4/80; PAD 12.10.4/70 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Mellon Foundation, Andrew W., 9/79 - 4/80; PAD 12.10.4/139 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 10/78 - 7/80; PAD 12.10.4/152 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - 1907 Foundation, 4/76 - 3/80; PAD 12.10.4/156 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 6/78 - 5/80; PAD 12.10.4/204 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Patent Administration, 1/80 - 8/80; PAD 12.11 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Patent Administration, 1/79 - 12/79; PAD 12.11 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Land and Buildings, 11/78 - 6/80; PAD 12.14 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Master Faculty Plan/Capital Funding, 1/79 - 1/80; PAD 12.14.1/1 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Buildings, Building Space, 11/78 - 7/80; PAD 12.14.7 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Facilities Planning/Monthly Project Report, 9/78 - 8/80; PAD 12.14.7/4 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Facilities Planning, 3/79 - 7/80; PAD 12.14.7/29 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Jasper Ridge Bio. Exper. Area (primate), 5/78 - 6/80; PAD 12.14.7/43 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Visiting Committee of the SU Libraries, 7/79; PAD 13.10.5/9 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Provost's Office, 1/79 - 7/80; PAA 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Provost's Office, 6/78 - 12/78; PAA 1 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Provost's Senior Staff, 9/78 - 8/80; PAA 1.4.2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Dean's Council Agenda File #3, 9/78 - 4/80; PAA 1.5.1 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Dean's Council Agenda, 1/76 - 6/78; PAA 1.5.1 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Dean's Retreat (Acad. Leadership Conf.), 8/74 - 1/78; PAA 1.5.3 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Office of Undergraduate Studies, 2/79 - 5/80; PAA 1.12 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Divisions, 9/78 - 7/80; PAA 1.13 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Students, 11/78 - 4/80; PAA 1.13.2 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Lists/Statistical Reports, 6/79 - 4/80; PAA 2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Emeriti, 9/78 - 8/80; PAA 2.2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Appointments, 4/75 - 6/79; PAA 2.3 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Appointments, 10/78- 8/79; PAA 2.3 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Faculty and Acad. Appoint. Procedures and Policies, 1/79 - 6/80; PAA 2.3.2 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Franklin, H. Bruce: Hearing, 6/73 - 7/80; PAA 2.6.2/1 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - University Fellows, 4/79 - 10/79; PAA 2.9 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Stanford National Ratings and Accred., 10/77 - 8/80; PAA 3.4 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Stanford National Ratings and Accred., 10/77 - 12/79; PAA 3.5.1 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 10/78 - 6/80; PAA 4.1 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Art & Architecture, 1/79 - 6/80; PAA 4.1.9 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Rodin Collection/Cantor Gift, 6/79 - 6/80; PAA 4.1.9/1 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Linguistics, 3/79 - 6/80; PAA 4.1.11 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Biological Sciences, 1/79 - 7/80; PAA 4.1.12 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Chemistry, 3/79 - 6/80; PAA 4.1.13 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Communication, 4/78 - 8/80; PAA 4.1.15 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Computer Science, 1/79 - 6/80; PAA 4.1.17 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Economics, 1/79 - 8/80; PAA 4.1.20 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - English, 6/79 - 8/80; PAA 4.1.21 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - French and Italian, 12/78 - 8/80; PAA 4.1.22 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - German, 1/79 - 6/80; PAA 4.1.24 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Mathmatics, 9/78 - 8/80; PAA 4.1.27 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Hopkins Marine Biology Center, 9/79 - 7/80; PAA 4.1.28 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Hopkins Marine Biology Center, 9/78 - 7/80; PAA 4.1.28 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Physics, 1/79 - 7/80; PAA 4.1.33 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Psychology, 4/78 - 11/79; PAA 4.1.35 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Sociology, 10/78 - 8/80; PAA 4.1.40 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Religious Studies, 9/78 - 6/80; PAA 4.1.47 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Graduate school of Business, 10/78 - 8/80; PAA 4.2 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - School of Earth Sciences, 1/79 - 8/80; PAA 4.3 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - School of Engineering, 1/80 - 12/80; PAA 4.4 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - School of Engineering, 9/78 - 9/79; PAA 4.4 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Engineering Economics, 3/76 - 8/80; PAA 4.4.4 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1/79 - 8/80; PAA 4.4.5 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Center for Material Research, 2/79 - 8/80; PAA 4.4.7 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 10/78 - 5/80; PAA 4.4.9 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Center for Integrated Systems, 1/80 - 6/80; PAA 4.4.19 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Center for Integrated Systems, 8/79 - 12/79; PAA 4.4.19 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Center for Integrated Systems Development, 3/79 - 12/79; PAA 4.4.19 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - School of Education, 1/80 - 6/80; PAA 4.5 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - School of Education, 2/79 - 12/79; PAA 4.5 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Center for Integrated Systems Dev., 11/78 - 2/79; PAA 4.4.19 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - School of Medicine, 11/78 - 12/78; PAA 4.6 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - School of Medicine, 7/78 - 10/78; PAA 4.6 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - School of Medicine, 5/79 - 8/79; PAA 4.6 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - School of Medicine, 1/79 - 3/79; PAA 4.6 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - School of Medicine, 1/80 - 4/80; PAA 4.6 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - School of Medicine, 4/80 - 6/80; PAA 4.6 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Food Research Institute, 12/78 - 6/80; PAA 4.8 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Hoover Institution, 10/78 - 7/80; PAA 4.9 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Center for Research in Inter. Studies, 10/78 - 7/80; PAA 4.10 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Arms Control & Disarmament Program, 8/78 - 12/79; PAA 4.10.1 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Program on U.S.-China Relations, 10/78 - 8/80; PAA 4.10.3 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - N.E. Asia-US forum (NEXUS), 12/79 - 6/80; PAA 4.10.3 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Program on Inter. Sci., Technology and Strategic Studies, 8/78 - 6/79; PAA 4.10.4 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Middle Eastern Studies/Pharoan, 10/79 - 2/80; PAA 4.10.5 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Libraries, 1/79 - 6/80; PAA 4.12 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - RLG/RLIN, 10/79 - 8/80; PAA 4.12.1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Ballots/Library Automation Project, 10/78 - 7/80; PAA 4.12.1 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 6/79 - 7/80; PAA 4.13 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 1/79 - 5/79; PAA 4.13 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 9/78 - 1/79; PAA 4.13 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - School of Law, 9/78 - 7/80; PAA 4.15 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Stanford University Hospital, 9/78 - 8/80; PAA 4.17 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Hospital: Board of Directors, 10/78 - 7/80; PAA 4.17.2 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - CIT (SCIP -- SHAW), 8/79 - 8/80; PAA 4.22 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Center for Information Processing (SCIP), 10/78 - 7/80; PAA 4.22 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Awards and Prizes, Misc., 2/77 - 1/80; PAA 5 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Fellowships, Misc./General Info, 10/78 - 2/80; PAA 8 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Endowed Chairs, Professorships, 1/79 - 5/80; PAA 10 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Endowed Chairs, Professorships, 9/78 - 12/78; PAA 10 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - California State Government, 1/79 - 8/80; G1.2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - US Government Relations, 1/79 - 8/79; G3 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - US Government Relations, 9/79 - 3/80; G3 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - US Government Relations, 4/80 - 8/80; G3 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Department of Health, Ed. & Welfare, 10/79 - 8/80; G3.8 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Department of Health, Ed. & Welfare, 1/79 - 6/79; G3.8 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - HEW -Office of Civil Rights, 1/79 - 7/80; G3.8.1 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - National Institute of Health, 2/79 - 7/80; G3.8.2 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Department of Education, 7/79 - 8/80; G3.8.3 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Department of Education, 8/78 - 6/79; G3.8.3 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Office of Education (HEW), 2/79 - 2/80; G3.8.4 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Department of Labor, 7/79 - 4/80; G3.12 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - National Science Foundation (HEW), 1/79 - 5/80; G 3.19 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Palo Alto, City of: Comm. Relations, 2/79 - 7/80; G 4.2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Countries, Governments/Misc., 4/79 - 7/80; G 5 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - China, 1/79 - 7/80; G 5.2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Conference, 1/79 - 5/80; AL 1.7 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - The Stanford Magazine, 1/79 - 7/80; AL 1.12 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Associates, 1/79 - 7/80; AL 2 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Association, 10/79 - 6/80; AL 3 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Clubs, Misc., 1/79 - 11/79; AL 3.4 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Clubs, Misc., 1979 -; AL 3.4 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Students, Misc., 1/79 - 7/80; ST 1 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - ASSU General, 10/79 - 5/80; ST 2 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - ASSU General, 1/79 - 8/79; ST 2 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - ASSU Elections and Referendums, 8/72 - 5/80; ST 2.4 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - ASSU Committee on Nominations, 4/79 - 6/80; ST 2.7 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - ASSU: Council of Presidents, 1/79 - 5/80; ST 2.8 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - ASSU Senate, 11/76 - 7/80; ST 2.10 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Bechtel International Center, 3/79 - 7/80; ST 3.5 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - KZSU (Radio), 3/79 - 6/80; ST 3.18 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - ARLO: Action Research Liaison Office, 2/79 - 5/80; ST 4.1 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Freshmen, 3/79 - 9/79; ST 5.3 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Senior Class, 12/79 - 1/80; ST 5.4 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Unidentified Folder (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2018-038
  Scope and Contents
  Remarks given at Fairmont Hotel Grand Ballroom.
  - Remarks to Alumni Group (1/3), 1971 Feb 17 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Remarks to Alumni Group (2/3), 1971 Feb 17 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Remarks to Alumni Group (3/3), 1971 Feb 17 (Box 1, Folder 3)